What's up
Everyone today
I'm going to walk you through ultra luxury department store for millionaires
Parrots here in the knightsbridge section of london
It's the holiday season
November twelfth
Twenty twenty three
About one
Fifteen p
M
Let's go inside
I heard their food haul is amazing
I have no idea what to expect in this department store
It's my first time
Well
This is interesting
I heard their food hall is on the first floor
I love this teddy bear exhibit
They have
This is cartier
So far everything i see in this department store is luxury and it's designed super well
If you want luxury
You have it here in harris
Yeah
And then the next thing that
Oh
The dining hall is that way
Let's take a look
You can easily spend a whole day here
Just eating
What do we have here
Chocolates
Am i right
This is
Uh
One of the
And it was
You tell
These are pricey pastries for sure
And now we have the cake section
A whole cake is eighty pounds
The honey cake
The red velvet cake
Thank you
This is where you pay for your items
Now you have to wonder
Is this a department store or food hall
I think it's both
And they do it very well
Everything here looks
Very tasty and good
Actually their phones aren't a bad price
And the baked items
What's this
The food market
Go ahead
They even have deli meats here
So far i am impressed
I never think i'd see a food hall like this and start a department store
The only thing that's really come close to this in my experience
Being from new york is the grand central market inside
Grand central terminal
But that really isn't connected to any shopping
Can even get fish here
And you can tell it is fresh
That salmon is so pink
It is a rather odd place to put that food hall right
In the middle of the perfume section and the sunglasses
Is this an egyptian temple or a pyramid
What is going on here
What a central escalator
This video doesn't do it
Justice folks
So you have to be here to look at all the angles
First floor woman's
Let's just take a quick look around the woman's floor
You can easily spend your life savings here
I'm telling you
The super brands on on this section
What can be more super brands than this chanel and louis vuitton
Now i'm curious
What the men's section looks like
There are six floors in this department store
There's also a hair salon on the on the fifth floor
Oh
A spend essential
Meaning you're going to have to spend for a luxury brand
Which doesn't really seem too essential to me
But let's take a look anyway
For i feel that you are the one
Now i need to see the last
Wow
Look at these sweaters
You can see all the detailed threads in there
And if you want great sweaters
Holo ralph lauren has it
We have to share my
Looks like there's the escalator on the other side
The hans road
Let's go back to the central escalator
Plus we'll also get to walk through the men's section
A little bit more on the way there
You can check out the super brand sue
Okay
I think the central escalator is this way
That's where
Let's
Sensual escalator
I'm still getting lost on the way
The escalator
The second view
The short time right
Yeah
We go up on
There is no wrong way to go about
Still can't get over this escalator
Wow
Look at that design at the top
It's like a zodiac
Oh
We have to check this section out for the toys
If harris brands itself as a christmas destination
They have to have good toys
Two thousand two hundred and fifty pounds for a unicorn
These are some of the best toys i've ever seen
Wow
It just came out
Uh
Two weeks ago
Yeah
This was
Uh
Five hundred and fifty dollars
I'm from the us
So
So thank you
Yeah
I'm doing a vlog of paris my first time here
Amazing the food hall downstairs
That as you use when it goes up again for the killing them
Sure this has to be the most impressive toy collection i've seen in a department store
Can't get anywhere else
Yeah
You can
I even feel like a kid again coming through these aisles
So if you want to go to the left and you go left right
Hot wheels
Arts and crafts
And it flies around what
Oh my gosh
Yeah
When you're a baby
This is incredible
What does this feel like
Wow
It's cold too
He gets oh with water
Drink the water
Yeah
Whoa
Got warm
It drives back down into the powder
You use regular water again
And you can keep using it
Like wow
Oh my god mom
Feel it
This is amazing to try it
Yeah
It's
There we go
Yeah
We'll just add regular
And it cleans right off too
Exactly three
It
But now that is over and over again
It doesn't stick to your clothing
It's non toxic
Thank you
There are many instructions
So you might get a little flu
I'm enjoying the toy section more than the food
Haha ha ha ha
And that goes to tell you something
See you bye bye
I want to continue on that central escalator
But that's so cool
Oh
There
It is past
The mini super brands
If you want to splurge for the young ones
You can do it here
I think this is the last um set
Escalator set only goes goes up to the fifth floor
Let's take a look at harrods on the way down
That was good
Oh
This is something i didn't see before the basil street escalator
So this is the only way you can get to this floor with a basil street
Escalator
Lots of perfumes
Look at that gorgeous chandelier down the hall
I don't even know what i'm smelling walking down this hallway
There's so many sweet fragrances all over the place
All right
I think i'm gonna turn around now and take the escalator back down
But i'm really impressed with this department store
It's incredible
If you're in london
You have to check this place out
No question about it
Even if you don't intend to buy anything
Just going by the um
The food hall is just an incredible experience
You go by that food hall
This is
All right
Everyone
I hope you enjoy that tour of harrods department store
What a place
Thank you so much for watching
It's been an incredible experience
Going in here for the first time
With you all hit that like button subscribe
And i will see you next time bye
Everyone take care
Now that she's holding a go
It's not want you to my cause
I like it
But i like it